bellstrike.com 2011-12-04

# Privacy Policy | Bellstrike

### 1\. Introduction

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully before using the Bellstrike website Service offered by Zekten, LLC. Your (“You” or “Your”) privacy concerns are important to Zekten LLC (“We,” “Us,” or “Our”) and protecting your privacy and safeguarding your information is one of Our highest goals. You need to know what information is being collected about You through Our Website (“Service”) and how Your information may be used. To that end, this Privacy Policy explains what information We may collect about You.

### 2\. Collection of Information

In connection with Your use of the Service, You will provide the majority of the information We collect about You. For example, We may require You to provide certain information, including, but not limited to, Your name, mailing address, e-mail addresses, telephone number and other personally identifiable information. Other information collected by Us may be provided automatically when You access the Service, such as observing Your use of the Service, through the use of cookies (described below), and may be obtained from other sources such as Our business partners. We do not require you provide personal information to visit our Web site; however, You may choose to provide Us with personal information through an email message, form, survey, registration process, etc. This information is used only to fulfill the stated purpose of Your communication, participation or used certain aspects of the Service. Additionally, You may also choose to provide information to Us through the APIs of popular social networks such as Facebook or Twitter. We will abide by all of the terms of service and privacy of those APIs. As a condition to using certain features of our Services You may be required to provide certain personal information to nonprofits, such as Your e-mail address, country of residence and zip/postal code ("Donor Information") in order to join the nonprofit’s mailing list. As a condition to each such nonprofit's right to receive such Donor Information, Zekten requires each nonprofit to agree that it 1) will not not disclose, rent, or sell any Donor Information to any third party, 2) will use the Donor Information only in connection with the nonprofit's mailing list, in order to provide fans with general information and news about the nonprofit, and 3) will ensure that any e-mail sent to its mailing list will include a mechanism by which the recipient can unsubscribe from the mailing list, along with clear instructions on how to do so (i.e. a functioning "opt-out" mechanism). However, Zekten has no control over and no liability for the use of the Donor Information by the nonprofits. You can choose not to provide such Donor Information, but You may not be able to take advantage of the associated features. 

### 3\. No Collection of Children's Personal Information

Our Services are intended for general audiences and nonprofit commercial use. We do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 18. We reserve the right to delete any information We believe to be in violation of this Privacy Policy.

### 4\. Use of Information

We automatically collect and temporarily store information about Your visit. The information We collect enables Us to refine and offer better services to You. We may share the information We collect about You with Our business partners. The types of information we collect include, but are not limited to:

  * Date and time of Your visit
  * IP addresses
  * Browser type, operating system, and language
  * Pages You visited
  * Address of the website from which You came

### 5\. Security

Your Zekten account information is protected by a password for Your privacy and security. You need to prevent unauthorized access to your account and personal information by selecting and protecting Your password appropriately and limiting access to Your computer and browser by signing off after You have finished accessing Your account.

Zekten endeavors to protect user information to ensure that user account information is kept private, however, Zekten cannot guarantee the security of user account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time.

The Service may contain links to other sites. Zekten is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site You should read the privacy policy stated on that site. This Privacy Policy only governs information collected on this Service.

### 6\. Cookies

When You visit the Service, We may place a text file called a “cookie” on Your computer's hard drive. A cookie is a small piece of information that a web-service can store on Your web browser and later retrieve. A cookie enables the Service to recognize You as a prior user, provides the Service with information regarding Your prior use and assists Us in determining what portions of the Service are most appropriate for You. Your Web browser may provide You with the ability to not accept cookies. However, in order to take full advantage of the Service, We recommend that You accept cookies from the Service.

### 7\. Disclosure

We do not sell, license, lease or otherwise disclose Your information to any other parties; except that We may disclose Your information when We believe, in good faith, that disclosure is reasonably necessary to comply with laws, law enforcement or court orders, or to protect the rights, property or safety of another person, including Our own property or rights.

### 8\. No Liability

We have made significant investments in protecting and safeguarding Your information. We continuously upgrade and enhance Our security measures as new tools, techniques and technology become available. However, We do not guaranty that any such information will not be misused or disclosed to third parties. We will not have any liability to You for any such misuse or disclosure. 

### 9\. Consent

By using the Service, You consent to the collection and use of Your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. If We decide to change this Privacy Policy, which We may do at any time without notice to You, We will post those changes on this page. By continuing to use the Service after We have posted the changes, You agree to and accept such changes. You should periodically check the Service for changes to this Privacy Policy.

### 10\. Additional Information

We welcome your questions, comments and requests for additional information regarding privacy of the Service.

You accept and agree to be bound this Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions of Use.
